This is the story of little Runa Sasaki, a young girl with an overprotective mother and a father with a gentle heart.
Thanks to them and her older brother, who's always a step ahead and looking after her, Miss Runa was brought up in this world like a princess.
Some of the things she loves are the chocolate donuts from the venerable neighborhood donut shop, the online games she excels at.
And especially her gamer friends who always treat her so kindly.
As for unfamiliar places, unfamiliar things, and unfamiliar people, she hates them.
Growing up, little Runa Sasaki was a coddled child.
As a result, she believes if she keeps quiet and puts on airs, someone is bound to show her kindness.
But this sets Runa apart from her classmates who don't really know what to make of her.
At times, she was the target of bullying from the older students.
However, since she has 300 friends online, this never really bothered her.
Even if the girls who'd been her classmates for all three years were...
Miss Sasaki, you're on duty today, right?
Are you going to clear the blackboard?
Oh, right. Still calling her by her last name?
It doesn't really bother Runa.
By the way, little Runa Sasaki was born blessed with breathtakingly pretty features.
So many of the boys in her grade have developed a secret crush on her.
But as her casual attire, which she can be seen wearing on school trips, is of the hardcore Lolita variety,
and since her hair color is slightly different than the other girls, the boys end up keeping their distance from her.
On top of that, Runa's older brother is charmingly handsome, and this friend who she's known since childhood is a knockout.
In her eyes, they've become the standard for all guys.
Which means that the boys in her class all look like this to her.
Hey, look you guys! I recorded a new video!
Aw, that's so adorable!
I was dancing with you, Kachi!
You tried too!
Just watch!
First you go like this, and…
What are those moves?
Oh no, I'm gonna be late!
Ah-chan, Makolin, see you!
Yeah, later, Lee-chan!
Bye-bye!
Uh, see you later too, Miss Sasaki!
Good luck!
You bet!
But the truth about little Runa Sasaki…
Bye-bye…
Is that she's a lion at home and a mouse outside, spoiled and cowardly.
Coming!
Recently, though, Runa met someone new.
Hey, Runa, you made it!
And became friends with a girl who's a bit older than her.
I got you some of that new pudding from the convenience store!
Since Akane is a little more grown up than the other girls in Runa's class…
Akane!
I saw this weird dance at school today.
Oh yeah? You wanna show me?
She's always nice to Runa, even when she can be mean or acts like a spoiled child.
Because of this, Runa is somewhat aware that even though they're friends now,
they're not exactly on equal footing.
Oh yeah, and you know what else?
Hey, hold up a sec.
My friend just sent me something.
But since Akane is neither family nor a childhood friend…
It's not like she's going to act the way Runa wants her to.
Who is this other friend?
Respond to them later!
They're with Runa right now!
And it's not like she'll take the time to comfort her when she gets pouty and sulky either.
Actually, she doesn't even notice her sulking.
Ugh! Runa! Check this out!
They're shooting a TV show in front of the station!
And that super hot actor Sato is there!
You wanna go see?
I didn't know you were such a big fangirl, Akane.
I sure am! Are you with me?
But…
Come on, hurry, hurry!
Just wait a minute!
It's a little different than when she's with her brother and friends!
There's a new kind of excitement!
Even though she supposedly doesn't like unfamiliar things or unfamiliar people!
Even from far away, Sato really is so dreamy!
You really think so?
Yamada's way better looking though!
Sure he is, but Yamada's Yamada, you know?
Yeah, that's true…
Oh, hey! Check out those people over there!
They're dancing! Doesn't that look fun?
Runa doesn't understand why anyone would dance in the street.
I don't know, don't you wanna jump in with that weird dance you showed me?
Not in your life!
Was it like this?
No, like this!
But here lately…
She's beginning to think that it could actually be fun if she made more friends who'd do this weird dance with her.
Just a tiny bit.
I really want to fall in love.
According to the life plan I put together, I'm supposed to be getting married as soon as I graduate from college.
My mom had me when she was in her early twenties, so to be like her, I've always wanted to get married as young as possible.
But before that can even happen, I'd need to find myself a husband, right?
And to lock down a husband by then, I need a boyfriend first, don't I?
That's why more than anything, I really want to fall in love…
Uh, wait a sec. You should let the attacker finish it off.
Right. Now you're almost there.
I did it! The quest is cleared!
Neither of you nerds heard a single word I just said, did you?
Oh, sorry. Check it out, Momo.
I've managed to reach level 50 in just a week, isn't that so…
Not interested. Keep following Runa's instructions and you can max out your level by the end of the month.
Akane.
This is your precious free day. Are you sure you should be binging on an online game with a runaway middle school kid?
Oh, she's not a runaway. She had an argument with her brother, so it's awkward for her at home, you know?
Fine, but she's still a child. I mean, what does playing online games with her say about the two of us?
If this is boring you so badly, why don't you just go home? You didn't have a good reason for coming here anyway.
Quiet, you.
Don't mess with me, little girl.
You don't know how lucky you are, Akane. Wish I could meet a handsome young guy.
Do you mean Yamada? Trust me, it isn't like that, okay?
Although we have gotten a little closer lately, and he let me add him to my friends list.
But he's as surly as ever, and he still won't go hunting with me either.
Well, that's because your levels are too far apart, and it wouldn't be very profitable for him.
But whenever I ask him about equipment, he gives me all kinds of advice. He's actually surprisingly helpful.
Really? As long as I've known him, Yamada's never been anything but helpful.
Even though he's studying for his own entrance exams, he still comes to tutor Runa, too.
Huh? He must be super popular.
Yeah, he was beyond popular, but I've never seen him with a girlfriend, so he must be pretty awkward with girls.
What? That's such a waste! Maybe I'll volunteer for the job.
Hmm? Speak of the devil.
Speak of the devil.
Hey there! Yamada!
Hey.
It sure has been a while since I've seen you online.
I guess so. I've been busy lately.
Hey, listen! I finally got my shoes all upgraded, like you taught me the other day!
Hmm.
It is? But I was supposed to use int gems like you, wasn't I?
I thought I did it just how you showed me.
I use ints because I'm playing a wizard, but a paladin should be using vits.
Huh? Then I can't use these gems?
But I worked so hard to collect them, too.
Do you want to use my spare pair of shoes?
I have a set that's been fully upgraded for tank classes.
Hmm.
It's okay.
I just have to collect those vip things, right?
In that case, I'm gonna go hunting again to collect them.
It'll be easy now that I know where they drop.
Yeah, of course. Sorry about that. I was out of line.
Good luck with your upgrades.
A smiley-faced emote? That never happens!
Now she's screaming to herself. Is she finally having a breakdown?
She's having fun.
This is so boring! All you've done today is play that game! I want to go outside or go on a group date or something!
You want to give it a try, Momo? It's actually pretty fun.
You know games aren't my thing!
Oh, come on! Just try it out!
But I'm clueless when it comes to computers!
Once you get the hang of it, they're easy to operate!
Here, look. I'm going on a hunt now, so watch me!
I don't know the first thing about computers and stuff, but it's a bad sign if there's smoke coming out, right?
Akanechi's computer had a breakdown?
Yeah, it exploded in her face while she was playing boss.
Makes sense. The last update really puts a strain on outdated hardware.
I guess her system couldn't handle it.
She says she won't be able to play again until she saves up enough for a new one.
Seemed like it made her really sad.
Coming!
Who is it?
Hello.
I heard you're in need of a repairman, so...
Ta-da!
I can remember.
I remember.
I'll run away.
Part Goodbye.
Take one.
My name is Olaus אנis.
Him.
I am.
I'm not.
Yes?
Good morning, Yamada.
Hey, what's going on?
By chance, you don't have a used computer, do you?
Like an old spare?
No, I don't.
The little birdie told me that Akanechi's computer broke down.
Apparently it was smoking and everything.
There was smoke?
Coming from where?
I haven't seen it myself, so I don't know.
So, do you think you could take a look at Akanechi's computer when you have time?
Me?
You might be able to fix it by just swapping out a part.
Wouldn't it be better if you went, Eita?
I mean, I wouldn't mind going.
But what if there was some sort of misunderstanding?
You know, how would it look with a healthy guy going into a sweet college girl's apartment?
That seems risky.
What kind of guy do you think I am?
A new breed.
Runa mentioned that she was really depressed about it.
Akanechi's been grinding really hard and fast lately, so I feel bad for her.
Stop by after Runa's tutoring session, will ya?
I'll have Runa take you over to her apartment when you're done.
Okay?
Pretty please?
Mm-mm.
It's okay.
I just have to collect those vid things, right?
In that case, I'm going to go hunting again to collect them.
You came to fix my computer, Yamada?
Yeah, and Runa's the one who brought him over!
I'm only here to take a look.
Please don't get your hopes up.
Runa did!
Oh, don't look at me like that.
Seriously, I don't even know if I can fix it yet.
Runa!
So it's a laptop.
Feel free to make yourselves at home, okay?
Do either of you want some snacks?
Please, don't trouble.
I do!
Yamada is such a good person!
Akane, Akane!
So, uh, hanging up in your room there, are those...
Okay?
Thank goodness, he didn't notice.
Well, it's Yamada, so he wouldn't care anyway.
It does feel a little strange having Yamada in the house, but remember what Runa said.
He's awkward with girls.
I shouldn't be too self-conscious around him, or he'll get uncomfortable.
Just be me.
Hey, have the two of you eaten anything yet today?
If you haven't, I wouldn't mind whipping something up.
I can eat!
What do you say, Yamada?
You want something?
Yes, I would like some.
Well, well, how rare!
No thanks.
I forgot to tell you this before.
Hmm?
That curry you gave me, it was really tasty.
Sorry, I just remembered, so I forgot to bring back your containers.
I'm glad!
I'll pour my heart and soul into making lunch, so eat up, okay?
Hey, so listen.
There's a new girl who's going to be joining our guild.
Huh?
She's a really sweet-natured girl, and she's just so cute!
Kurihime!
The stranger yelled at me at the dungeon again!
I'm against bullying noobies!
One thing's for certain, she totally wears her heart on her sleeve.
Or should I say, she doesn't really hide who she is.
Yeah, a straightforward girl like her would be a good match for you, Akito.
I refuse to accept a stranger like that!
Who are you supposed to be, a sister-in-law?
I'm not interested.
It looks like the adapter pin's completely melted.
When did you buy this laptop?
Well, it was back when I started college, so I would say...
It's happening!
Love comedy.
Would that be...
Like this?
You've never cleaned your keyboard once, have you?
I didn't know you were supposed to!
There are traces of a spill.
No, stop!
Don't look close!
We sure are having another lovely day!
Akane?
What's up?
Lunch is almost ready.
I was wondering, do you have plans to take a bath anytime soon?
Not especially.
I'm cooking right now, so I'll be taking a bath later tonight.
Yamada, are you going to take a bath?
No, I'm not.
I don't really get it, so whatever.
Akane, can I have a slice of bread, please?
Be my guest.
Aren't you going to get full eating all that before this?
I'm making all my rice now.
Don't worry, I'm not the one who'll be eating it.
What?
Oh!
Why did you eat it all?
Why did you make me eat it?
Hey, come over here for a sec!
Hold on!
You've got to get a little bit closer or there won't be a lucky birth moment!
It's dangerous!
What do you mean?
Huh, now what am I supposed to do?
Hey!
You need to stop right now!
Ouch!
Yamada, what's wrong?
Your hair hit my eyeball.
No way!
Sorry!
Are you okay?
How's your eye?
Let me see it.
Which eye?
I'm fine.
Oh crap!
I panicked and grabbed his face without thinking!
I wonder if stuff like that really bothers him or something!
I am so sorry, Yamada!
Come on, I'm gonna make you apologize too!
I'm sorry!
I'll tie my hair up, okay?
Yes?
Excuse me, I'm heading back home for a bit.
I didn't bring over any of the tools I need, so...
Oh, but...
I'll be right back.
Wait, you don't have to do that!
Isn't going back and forth a-
Don't worry, it's not far.
It's almost like he was trying to run away.
Then you think so too, huh?
You really must have been uncomfortable.
So it's true that he's awkward with women.
I wish I hadn't done that to him.
Girls like Akanechi, who have less hair to deal with, can use this kind of pin to tie their hair up simply.
But girls like Miss Runa, who have an unruly massive hair, turn out like this.
Girls who have a whole bunch of hair have a hard time putting it up in ponytails.
I'm really jelly that you don't have to deal with this, Akane.
But isn't it better to have more?
Nah, not really.
There's no end to a young girl's anxieties.
Ah.